{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "b",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Play games",
                "Read books",
                "Solve maths problems",
                "Do projects"
            ],
            "question": "If you enjoy learning new stories and increasing knowledge, you should...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "a",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Do projects",
                "Solve maths problems",
                "Read books",
                "Play games"
            ],
            "question": "Working on assignments together in a team is called...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "c",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Good for",
                "Fun",
                "Useful",
                "Interesting"
            ],
            "question": "Studying hard and practicing skills are very ... for your future.",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "d",
            "img_src": "",
            "options": [
                "Do projects",
                "Play games",
                "Solve maths problems",
                "Group work"
            ],
            "question": "When students work together to complete a task, they are doing ...",
            "type": "multiple_choice"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Champion",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "The person who wins a competition is called a ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Close friends",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "People who share a strong bond and trust each other a lot are called ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Fun",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "Playing games is a great way to have ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Solve maths problems",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "If you enjoy working with numbers, you like to ...",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Play games",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "Many students love to ... during their free time because it is entertaining.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Do projects",
            "img_src": "",
            "question": "At school, students often work together to ... for different subjects.",
            "type": "short_answer"
        }
    ]
}